Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Exhibit Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, exhibit records
1987-2000
RU 332
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
The records consist of materials used for exhibits produced by Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-D (YRG 32-D), Records of Yale school and departmental libraries and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by exhibit.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of materials used for exhibits produced by Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Archives; Libraries -- Special collections; Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives; Yale University. Library -- Exhibitions
- Exhibit records, 1987-1998; Accession 1998-A-029
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Presidential Autographs, Douglas Campbell and Alfred W. Van Sinderen Collections, BRBL, 1987 September (Box 1)
  - Presidential Autographs, Douglas Campbell and Alfred W. Van Sinderen Collections, BRBL, 1987 September (Box 2)
  - Pancholi Collection of Gandhi Letters, 1991 January-February (Box 3)
  - "Picturing Africa: An Exhibit in Conjunction with the conference - 'Images and Empires: Visual Representations in and of Africa'", 1997 February-March (Box 4)
  - Innovation and Diversification: Yale during the Kingman Brewster Jr. Presidency, 1963-1977, 1998 February-April (Box 5)
  - Innovation and Diversification: Yale during the Kingman Brewster Jr. Presidency, 1963-1977, 1998 February-April (Box 6)
  - Innovation and Diversification: Yale during the Kingman Brewster Jr. Presidency, 1963-1977, 1998 February-April (Box 7)
- Photographs of items in Manuscripts and Archives' Paul Rand exhibition, 2000; Accession 2006-A-045
  - Photographs of Paul Rand exhibition, 2000 (Box 1)